<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>jonsalter.com</title>
    <link href="https://jonsalter.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://jonsalter.com" />
    <updated>2025-04-03T23:07:55+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Jon Salter</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://jonsalter.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Huge update</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/huge-update/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/huge-update/</id>

        <updated>2025-04-03T23:07:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Over the Winter a lot has changed both in my homelab and in the world. I'll try and get some pictures of my lab up&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Over the Winter a lot has changed both in my homelab and in the world. I'll try and get some pictures of my lab up before too long. Might make it more interesting. </p>
<p>I didn't do a lot of tinkering with my lab as I've been busy with family, but I've got a lot of plans with containers and services to start running. I've also gotten a Content Management System (CMS) for creating my website and uploading it easier. The only thing I really need is time so I can get things put together. I suppose that's the key hang up that everyone runs in to.</p>
<p>More to come.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/why/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/why/</id>

        <updated>2024-10-22T21:52:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    For some reason my site here went down and I still can’t seem to get my certificates for it working again. Got certificates working at&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For some reason my site here went down and I still can’t seem to get my certificates for it working again.<br>Got certificates working at home for all my services, so at least that’s cool. Certbot doesn’t seem to always want to renew when it should. Something for another day.<br>Ah well. Hopefully fixing this site won’t take very long - it took ten minutes after this post</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Holy shit</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/holy-shit/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/holy-shit/</id>

        <updated>2024-06-09T21:52:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I got certificates working in my home! I know it’s not the most complicated of things to most people, but it’s huge for me. Being&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I got certificates working in my home! I know it’s not the most complicated of things to most people, but it’s huge for me. <br>Being able to access things with trusted and auto-renewing certs is something that’ll make going forward with my homelab easier.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Finally; some progress</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/finally-some-progress/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/finally-some-progress/</id>

        <updated>2024-05-25T21:51:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Looks like I got TLS and my unique domain working. Between home life and other challenges this has taken quite a bit, but it’s there.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Looks like I got TLS and my unique domain working. Between home life and other challenges this has taken quite a bit, but it’s there. <br>Next up: I need certs for my internal domain/network</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Coming Soon</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/coming-soon/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/coming-soon/</id>

        <updated>2024-03-18T21:37:00+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    More will be made once I figure it out. Stay tuned
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    More will be made once I figure it out. Stay tuned
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
