<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>jonsalter.com</title>
    <link href="https://jonsalter.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://jonsalter.com" />
    <updated>2026-02-09T10:10:55+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Jon Salter</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://jonsalter.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Why do things break?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/why-do-things-break/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/why-do-things-break/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-09T10:10:55+02:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Proxmox clusters and falling apart. Name a more iconic duo. I updated my nodes last week and one of the nodes didn't come back up.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Proxmox clusters and falling apart. Name a more iconic duo.</p>
<p>I updated my nodes last week and one of the nodes didn't come back up. Okay, strange, but maybe it's some rando bug. The node was  rejecting SSH, but was responding to ping. So time to go local. The error seems to be corosync which is responsible for making sure nodes are communicating together properly. Troubleshooting has brought me to checking corosync.conf as well as corosync.service and the service seems to say that it's trying to run multiple copies of corosync at the same time. I'll have to go and copy the error messages for here later if I remember.</p>
<p>The best thing is that this node is the node I have Proxmox Backup Server on (which is not recommended for exactly this reason) which means I can't backup any of my clients and, if other times that this has happened are anything to go by, then I won't be able to restore them either. Now that I'm typing this out I'm wondering if maybe PBS is causing the issue. Guess I can try and stop PBS and see if that clears anything up?</p>
<p>Getting Linkedin to allow RSS feed uploading from my site to my feed apparently takes either a ton of posting or, I'm guessing, buying premium. Everyone under the sun wants subscriptions from us and that's getting real fucking annoying real fucking quick. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Is it a hobby when it&#x27;s also work?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/is-it-a-hobby-when-its-also-work/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/is-it-a-hobby-when-its-also-work/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T15:49:26+02:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I think so, especially when you consider how much time you have to sacrifice from your family and shit. "Do something you love and you'll&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I think so, especially when you consider how much time you have to sacrifice from your family and shit. "Do something you love and you'll never work a day in your life" is some bullshit. More like you'll work every day because you'll want to do it for play as well as for pay.</p>
<p>Trying to get services going in my stack and sometimes it's easy as cake, sometimes it's difficult as pie where you have to make the crust, filling, butter, and even pie tin from scratch. Some days you have an oven if you're lucky.</p>
<p>I suppose I should make some guides for the more complicated of my setup here. Maybe I'll make a section for that someday. I should also make a "to do" as a section so people can see where this is going to go. </p>
<p>Anyway, for this update: more services are going and more are being added. I'm going to try and focus, mostly, on easy wins so that I can have a more impressive stack. Once that's built up I can shift focus to things that didn't work the first time. Before I do that, however, I need to make sure that I'm getting a few things which I have priority for. Super important things like Floatplane Downloader. </p>
<p>Talked today with my partner about doing bug bounties for some extra income. Having playgrounds like I do is a good start to that, I think, but I wonder how tough it is to get paid for all that. I'm assuming it won't be so easy. Maybe I'll find out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Full Stack Redux and Talk Preparation</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/full-stack-redux-and-talk-preparation/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/full-stack-redux-and-talk-preparation/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-28T13:13:26+02:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I need to be better about consistency with updating here. Among other things. Doing homelab work while also working and having two kids kinda takes&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I need to be better about consistency with updating here. Among other things.</p>
<p>Doing homelab work while also working and having two kids kinda takes a lot of effort. I'm planning to have a VM with some AI assistance in the coming days to hopefully get things going quicker. So far dealing with Proxmox PCI passthrough has been an unnecessary pain in the dick. Passthrough to a VM is rather trivial, but passthrough to a container requires a PHD in Proxmoxology. Even following guides from Proxmox and others I couldn't get it to work properly. Ah well, soon I hope. </p>
<p>In the past year I've had to reflash my entire lab stack. When I did that there were two computers that didn't come back. Rather than try to fix them I e-wasted them which isn't preferable, but I have to be realistic about the amount of time I'd have to invest and how worth it that investment would end up being considering those two computers were both around ten years old. </p>
<p>Currently my lab has 4 nodes, 3 VMs, and 14 containers. Another 34 services are planned and will hopefully be along soon. I'd like to have 40+ services when I give my homelab presentation. </p>
<p>In order for the next steps: AI service, Linkedin connection with this website, and add on more and more services. </p>
<p>Then I'll have to update more often than once a year. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Huge update</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/huge-update/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/huge-update/</id>

        <updated>2025-04-03T23:07:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Over the Winter a lot has changed both in my homelab and in the world. I'll try and get some pictures of my lab up&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Over the Winter a lot has changed both in my homelab and in the world. I'll try and get some pictures of my lab up before too long. Might make it more interesting. </p>
<p>I didn't do a lot of tinkering with my lab as I've been busy with family, but I've got a lot of plans with containers and services to start running. I've also gotten a Content Management System (CMS) for creating my website and uploading it easier. The only thing I really need is time so I can get things put together. I suppose that's the key hang up that everyone runs in to.</p>
<p>More to come.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/why/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/why/</id>

        <updated>2024-10-22T21:52:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    For some reason my site here went down and I still can’t seem to get my certificates for it working again. Got certificates working at&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For some reason my site here went down and I still can’t seem to get my certificates for it working again.<br>Got certificates working at home for all my services, so at least that’s cool. Certbot doesn’t seem to always want to renew when it should. Something for another day.<br>Ah well. Hopefully fixing this site won’t take very long - it took ten minutes after this post</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Holy shit</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/holy-shit/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/holy-shit/</id>

        <updated>2024-06-09T21:52:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I got certificates working in my home! I know it’s not the most complicated of things to most people, but it’s huge for me. Being&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I got certificates working in my home! I know it’s not the most complicated of things to most people, but it’s huge for me. <br>Being able to access things with trusted and auto-renewing certs is something that’ll make going forward with my homelab easier.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Finally; some progress</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/finally-some-progress/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/finally-some-progress/</id>

        <updated>2024-05-25T21:51:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Looks like I got TLS and my unique domain working. Between home life and other challenges this has taken quite a bit, but it’s there.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Looks like I got TLS and my unique domain working. Between home life and other challenges this has taken quite a bit, but it’s there. <br>Next up: I need certs for my internal domain/network</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Coming Soon</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Salter</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://jonsalter.com/blog/coming-soon/"/>
        <id>https://jonsalter.com/blog/coming-soon/</id>

        <updated>2024-03-18T21:37:00+02:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    More will be made once I figure it out. Stay tuned
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    More will be made once I figure it out. Stay tuned
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
